Simon Fraser Student Society fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Publications, 1965 - 2009; F-74-12; 22 cm of textual records
  - Publications – general, 1965 - 2009; F-74-12-1; 12 cm of textual records
    - Purple Period / Purple Publication, 1965 - 1967; F-74-12-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-6.
    - Compass, 1966; F-74-12-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-5.
    - SFU Literary Magazine, 1966; F-74-12-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
    - Council Bulletin, 1966 - 1967; F-74-12-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-2.
    - Cheap Thrills, [ca 1967]; F-74-12-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
    - International Skyline, 1967; F-74-12-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
    - Makar, 1967; F-74-12-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
    - SFU Komix, 1969; F-74-12-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-7.
    - International Newsletter, 1980; F-74-12-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-4.
    - Identity – SFU Canadian-Persian Student Newspaper, 1998; F-74-12-1-0-10 (Newspaper box 74-35)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-item1.
    - Mountain Echoes – BC Student Multicultural Newspaper, 1999; F-74-12-1-0-11 (Newspaper box 74-35)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-item2.
    - U-Voice – SFU Chinese Student Newspaper, vol. 1, 1998 - 2009; F-74-12-1-0-12 (Newspaper box 74-35)
    - U-Voice – SFU Chinese Student Newspaper, vol. 2, 1998 - 2009; F-74-12-1-0-13 (Newspaper box 74-35)
    - U-Voice – SFU Chinese Student Newspaper, vol. 3, 1998 - 2009; F-74-12-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
  - Event flyers and notices, 1965 - 2004; F-74-12-2; 5 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of promotional material (notices, flyers, pamphlets, and leaflets) relating to events and activities sponsored by the SFSS or its clubs. Files include publications and newsletters, but no attempt was made by the creators to separate the material by organizational unit or publication title.
    - Event flyers, 1965 - 1968; F-74-12-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-11.
    - Event flyers, 1969 - 1971; F-74-12-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-12.
    - Event flyers, 1972 - 1974; F-74-12-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-28)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-13.
    - Event flyers, 1972 - 1976; F-74-12-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-14.
    - Event flyers, 1977 - 1978; F-74-12-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 74-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-15.
    - Event flyers, 1979 - 1989; F-74-12-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 74-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-16.
    - Event flyers, 1990 - 1991; F-74-12-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 74-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-17.
    - SFSS and student club notices, 1990 - 1996; F-74-12-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 74-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-34.
    - Event flyers, 1992; F-74-12-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-18.
    - SFSS and student club notices, 1997 - 2000; F-74-12-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 74-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-36.
    - SFSS and student club notices, 2001 - 2004; F-74-12-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 74-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-37.
  - Student almanacs, handbooks and guides, 1966 - 2005; F-74-12-3; 5 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of publications produced by the Society to inform students about SFSS activities, and SFU campus life and services. Includes student handbooks and guides, the 1967 student directory, a student-run teacher and course evaluation guide for 1978-79, and the annual SFSS Almanac that began in 1986-87 (not all years are included in the run).
    All files with one exception are open with no access restrictions. File F-74-12-3-0-3, Student Directory (1967) is restricted because it includes student numbers in a way that links them directly to named individuals. Under BC's subsequent privacy legislation (the Personal Information Protection Act applies to all organizations that are not public bodies, including SFSS), a student indentification number is personal information that must be protected. For more information on access, consult the reference archivist.
    - Student Guide, 1966 - 1967; F-74-12-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 74-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-9.
    - Handbook, 1966 - 1980; F-74-12-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 74-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-3.
    - Student Directory, 1967; F-74-12-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 74-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-8.
    - Teacher's Course Evaluation Guide, 1978 - 1979; F-74-12-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 74-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-10.
    - Student Handbook, 1985; F-74-12-3-0-5 (Archival box - small 74-36)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-33.
    - Almanac, 1986 - 1991; F-74-12-3-0-6 (Archival box - small 74-36)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-1.
    - Almanac, 1996 - 1997; F-74-12-3-0-7 (Archival box - small 74-36)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-35.
    - Almanac, 2003 - 2005; F-74-12-3-0-8 (Archival box - small 74-36)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-38.
    - Orientation Supplement to SFU Calendar, 1972-73, F-74-12-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 74-1)
  - Posters, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4; ca. 200 posters
    Sub-series consists of posters announcing or promoting events and activities sponsored by or relating to the Student Society. Events include SFSS meetings and elections, club activities, lectures, concerts, public meetings and protests, and pub and other campus events.
    - Posters, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-1
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-19.
    - Posters, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-2
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-20.
    - Posters, vol. 3, vol. 3, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-3
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-21.
    - Posters, vol. 4, vol. 4, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-4
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-22.
    - Posters, vol. 5, vol. 5, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-5
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-23.
    - Posters, vol. 6, vol. 6, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-6
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-24.
    - Posters, vol. 7, vol. 7, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-7
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-25.
    - Posters, vol. 8, vol. 8, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-8
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-26.
    - Posters, vol. 9, vol. 9, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-9
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-27.
    - Posters, vol. 10, vol. 10, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-10
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-28.
    - Posters, vol. 11, vol. 11, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-11
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-29.
    - Posters, vol. 12, vol. 12, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-12
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-30.
    - Posters, vol. 13, vol. 13, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-13
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-31.
    - Posters, vol. 14, vol. 14, 1969 - [197-?]; F-74-12-4-0-14
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-74-9-0-0-32.
  - Yearbooks, 1965-1967; F-74-12-5; 2 yearbooks
    Sub-series consists of the first (and only ) two issues of the Simon Fraser University Yearbook created and published by the Student Society. The yearbooks are hardcover bound volumes containing photographs, text and essays relating to aspects of campus life. The editors' intention was to create an annual yearbook, and volumes were produced for the first two years of the university's existence. The yearbook was discontinued after the second year (1966-67). The sub-series contains two hardcover copies of each yearbook; in 2015 the yearbooks were digitized
    The yearbooks (two copies of two issues) were originally arranged by the archivist as part of series 10 (Subject files), with separate file numbers (39–42) assigned to each physical item. In May 2016, the Archives made the digitized versions available, and the archivist assigned the yearbooks to a new sub-series (12-5), registering each issue as a separate item.
    Textual records; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    The yearbooks were digitized by the Archives in 2015. For the production master copy, a digital photograph was made for each page (in tiff format). From these a single pdf file was complied as the access copy. The production master copies are stored in the Archives' digital repository preservation system.
    - Simon Fraser University Yearbook 1965-66, 1966; F-74-12-5-0-0-1; F-74-10-0-0-39; F-74-10-0-0-40
    - Simon Fraser University Yearbook 1966-67, 1967; F-74-12-5-0-0-2; F-74-10-0-0-41; F-74-10-0-0-42; Trigger warning: archival records convey ideas and sentiments from the time period in which they were created. Some of the content in this file may be offensive and/or traumatizing (racial stereotypes, derogatory language). The Archives acknowledges that the content might be difficult and offers alternative means of access for those who don’t wish to approach the sensitive material in the file. Please contact the reference archivist for more details.